[Music]
foreign
the purpose
okay next
i would like also to introduce our
company which is fwd so means fresh and
innovative approach to life insurance so
it doesn't stand for anything
of the pacific century group an
asian-based investment company with the
businesses
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
okay
insurance life insurance companies
no because
the life is by insurance commission like
for instance for the longest time
in life
for the longest time
so see i see
swords nikonasana by they invited fwd
and during that time
the bsp would rather
logic partner
life insurance
[Music]
as i said they are being done
nothing
for that one
by insurance commission insurance
commission is very strict that's why
they have that
um they would want rather
i was part of it but they decided to
pack up
foreign
it will never happen
sales so any insurance company would
love to make salute
they're looking at the future now not my
future sales so
[Music]
the frontliners we don't know
it up
only the lightning students
and the nightlife i'm not like
okay everybody everybody needs it
a house
[Music]
foreign
just like my sister she got from this
for this much and for a number of years
now
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
we always hope for the best for our
children
and then
just to be
[Music]
okay
assessment management we have also the
technical media and technology so
but if there's something happen to the
insurance company of course the pacific
century
that's them
that's how they are
that's it
[Music]
number one
so